Office of the Board of Trustees Records UA003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Executive Committee, 1854 -- 2020; UA003.002; 12.55 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 46 Digital Object(s) 46 zip files containing 719 files.; 694 Megabytes
  - Working papers, 1954 -- 2000; UA003.002.001
    - Executive Committee, December 5, 1995; UA003.002.094.00025 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, January 16, 1996; UA003.002.094.00026 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, March 5, 1996; UA003.002.094.00027 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, April 2, 1996; UA003.002.094.00028 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, June 4, 1996; UA003.002.094.00029 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, September 10, 1996; UA003.002.094.00030 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, October 24, 1996; UA003.002.094.00031 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, January 7, 1997; UA003.002.094.00032 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, February 8, 1997; UA003.002.094.00033 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, February 13, 1997; UA003.002.094.00034 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, March 4, 1997; UA003.002.094.00035 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, March 28, 1997; UA003.002.094.00036 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, June 3, 1997; UA003.002.094.00037 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, September 9, 1997; UA003.002.094.00038 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, November 7, 1997; UA003.002.094.00039 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, January 8, 1998; UA003.002.094.00040 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, March 3, 1998; UA003.002.094.00041 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, July 17, 1998; UA003.002.094.00042 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, May 16, 1998; UA003.002.094.00043 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, September 3, 1998; UA003.002.094.00044 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, October 17, 1998; UA003.002.094.00045 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, November 23, 1998; UA003.002.094.00046 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, January 5, 1999; UA003.002.094.00047 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, March 15, 1999; UA003.002.094.00048 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, April 13, 1999; UA003.002.094.00049 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, June 1, 1999; UA003.002.094.00050 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, September 7, 1999; UA003.002.094.00051 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, October 5, 1999; UA003.002.094.00052 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, January 10, 2000; UA003.002.094.00053 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, January 21, 2000; UA003.002.094.00054 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, March 7, 2000; UA003.002.094.00055 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, July 7, 2000; UA003.002.094.00056 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, September 5, 2000; UA003.002.094.00057 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, 2005 -- 2007; UA003.002.124; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 124, Folder 1 - 21)
    - Executive Committee, 2007 -- 2010; UA003.002.125; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 125, Folder 14 - 40)
  - Correspondence, 1860 -- 1909; UA003.002.002
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence, 1860-1909, Appointments, Benefactors, UA003.002.029 (Box 29)
  - Meeting minutes, 1854 -- 1962; UA003.002.003
    - Executive Committee, 1910 -- 1913; UA003.002.085.00001 (Box 85)
    - Executive Committee, 1914 -- 1916; UA003.002.085.00002 (Box 85)
    - Executive Committee, 1917 -- 1919; UA003.002.085.00003 (Box 85)
    - Executive Committee, 1920 -- 1925; UA003.002.085.00004 (Box 85)
    - Executive Committee, 1949 -- 1950; UA003.002.085.00005 (Box 85)
    - Executive Committee, 1951 -- 1952; UA003.002.085.00006 (Box 85)
    - Executive Committee, 1952 -- 1953; UA003.002.085.00007 (Box 85)
    - Executive Committee, 1954; UA003.002.085.00008 (Box 85)
    - Executive Committee, 1955 -- 1956; UA003.002.085.00009 (Box 85)
    - Executive Committee, 1959 -- 1960; UA003.002.085.00010 (Box 85)
    - Executive Committee, 1961 -- 1962; UA003.002.085.00011 (Box 85)
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 1, 1854 -- 1866; UA003.002.112.00003 (Box UA003 Shared 3)
      July 14, 1854-February 12, 1866
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 3, 1873 -- 1877; UA003.002.112.00004 (Box UA003 Shared 3)
      October 6, 1873-May 4, 1877
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 4, 1878 -- 1889; UA003.002.112.00005 (Box UA003 Shared 3)
      September 17, 1878-January 29, 1889
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 5, 1889 -- 1896; UA003.002.112.00006 (Box UA003 Shared 3)
      February 26, 1889-October 23, 1896
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 6, 1896 -- 1900; UA003.002.112.00007 (Box UA003 Shared 3)
      November 24, 1896-January 9, 1900
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 7, 1900 -- 1902; UA003.002.112.00008 (Box UA003 Shared 3)
      January 18, 1900-April 17, 1902
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 8, 1902 -- 1905; UA003.002.112.00009 (Box UA003 Shared 3)
      May 22, 1902-February 16, 1905
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 9, 1905 -- 1908; UA003.002.112.00010 (Box UA003 Shared 3)
      March 2, 1905-March 8, 1908
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 10, 1908 -- 1910; UA003.002.112.00011 (Box UA003 Shared 3)
      June 4, 1908-October 20, 1910
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 11, 1910 -- 1916; UA003.002.113.00001 (Box 113)
      October 20, 1910-November 16, 1916
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 12, 1916 -- 1922; UA003.002.113.00002 (Box 113)
      December 21, 1916-January 26, 1922
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 13, 1922 -- 1930; UA003.002.113.00003 (Box 113)
      February 23, 1922-March 13, 1930
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 14, 1930 -- 1935; UA003.002.113.00004 (Box 113)
      April 17, 1930-May 10, 1935
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 15, 1935 -- 1942; UA003.002.113.00005 (Box 113)
      September 19, 1935-January 8, 1942
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 16, 1942 -- 1946; UA003.002.113.00006 (Box 113)
      January 22, 1942-August 26, 1946
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 17, 1946 -- 1949; UA003.002.113.00007 (Box 113)
      September 30, 1946-December 20, 1949
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 18, 1950 -- 1952; UA003.002.114.00001 (Box UA003 Shared 4)
      January 17, 1950-December 29, 1952
    - Executive committee minutes, volume 19, 1953 -- 1955; UA003.002.114.00002 (Box UA003 Shared 4)
      January 26, 1953-January 14, 1955
    - Executive Committee, meeting minutes, 1930 -- 1936; UA003.002.119.00001 (Box Volume 119)
  - Executive committee files, 2004-2016; UA003.002.00001; 407 Digital Object(s); 0.44 Gigabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2016; UA003.002.00002; 25 Digital Object(s); .02 Gigabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2017; UA003.002.00003; 7 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2017; UA003.002.00004; 4 Digital Object(s); 2.87 Megabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2017; UA003.002.00005; 3 Digital Object(s); 1.82 Megabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2017; UA003.002.00006; 12 Digital Object(s); 9.52 Megabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2017; UA003.002.00007; 6 Digital Object(s); 6.83 Megabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2017; UA003.002.00008; 6 Digital Object(s); 6.87 Megabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2017; UA003.002.00009; 5 Digital Object(s); 2.6 Megabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2017; UA003.002.00010; 16 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2017; UA003.002.00011; 10 Digital Object(s); 7.15 Megabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2018; UA003.002.00012; 8 Digital Object(s); 6.78 Megabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2018; UA003.002.00013; 9 Digital Object(s); 6.3 Megabytes
  - Executive committee files, 2018; UA003.002.00014; 9 Digital Object(s); 6.73 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, ballot vote, 2018-07-03; UA003.002.00015; 5 Digital Object(s); 3.82 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, ballot vote, 2018-07-27; UA003.002.00016; 4 Digital Object(s); 2.17 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, 2018-09-12; UA003.002.00017; 17 Digital Object(s); 16.46 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, 2018-10-11; UA003.002.00018; 6 Digital Object(s); 5.23 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, 2019-01-09; UA003.002.00019; 5 Digital Object(s); 3.94 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-01-14; UA003.002.00020; 4 Digital Object(s); 2.26 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, special session, 2019-01-21; UA003.002.00021; 4 Digital Object(s); 2.84 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, 2019-03-14; UA003.002.00022; 9 Digital Object(s); 7.55 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-04-02; UA003.002.00023; 5 Digital Object(s); 4.41 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, 2019 March 14; UA003.002330; 8.2 Megabytes 12 files
  - Executive Committee files, 2019-04-22; UA003.002.00024; 8 Digital Object(s); 4.96 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-05-03; UA003.002.00025; 5 Digital Object(s); 3.22 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-05-13; UA003.002.00026; 5 Digital Object(s); 3.45 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-06-26; UA003.002.00027; 6 Digital Object(s); 4.07 Megabytes
  - Executive Committee files, 2019 September 18; UA003.002331; 8.8 Megabytes 8 files
  - Executive Committee files, 2019 October 10; UA003.002332; 11.8 Megabytes 7 files
  - Executive Committee files, ballot vote, 2019 November 21; UA003.002333; 2.9 Megabytes 4 files
  - Executive Committee files, special session, 2019 November 25; UA003.002334; 1.5 Megabytes 2 files
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 January 14; UA003.002378; 9.19 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 February 05; UA003.002379; 2.1 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 February 06; UA003.002380; 1.53 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 February 21; UA003.002381; 745.7 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 March 12; UA003.002382; 14.81 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 April 01; UA003.002383; 3.35 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 April 08; UA003.002384; 2.66 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 April 17; UA003.002385; 3.05 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 May 29; UA003.002386; 2.44 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 June 08; UA003.002387; 5.64 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 August 13; UA003.002388; 1.94 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 September 09; UA003.002389; 8.62 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 9 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 October 07; UA003.002390; 6.35 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 12 files.
  - Executive Committee files, 2020 December 03; UA003.002391; 1.79 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
- Academic Affairs Committee, 1964 -- 2020; UA003.003; 23.3 Linear Feet; 48 Digital Object(s) 48 zip files containing 1,974 files.; 3.97 Gigabytes
  This series contains material from Tufts University's Academic Affairs Committee from the 1960s to 2000. Folders contain meeting announcements, agendas, minutes, letters, memoranda, and supplemental material (reports and memoranda regarding particular schools and faculty appointments). There is a small portion of this series from 1964 to 1984 subtitled the Education Policy Committee pertaining to academic affairs. The Academic Affairs Committee replaced the Educational Policy Committee in 1982.
  Also includes operating reports and correspondence of the Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis, Inc. IFPA, founded in 1976, "is an independent, nonpartisan research organization that conducts research, publishes studies, convenes seminars and conferences, promotes education, and trains policy analysts in the fields of foreign policy and national security affairs." (IFPA Homepage, Available:http://www.ifpa.org/). The Institute maintains a core staff of specialists at its offices in Cambridge, Massachusetts and Washington, D.C. IFPA is an affiliate of the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy. Fletcher School faculty and deans have served on the Institution's Board of Directors and Board of Research Consultants. This was an organization supported by the Overseers of the Corporation.
  - IFPA, 1980 -- 1992; UA003.003.001
    - IFPA, October 6, 1980; UA003.003.050.00001 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, December 15, 1980; UA003.003.050.00002 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, January 1, 1981; UA003.003.050.00003 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, April 1, 1981; UA003.003.050.00004 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, July 30, 1981; UA003.003.050.00005 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, October 1, 1981; UA003.003.050.00006 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, January 1, 1982; UA003.003.050.00007 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, March 31, 1982; UA003.003.050.00008 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, July 1, 1982; UA003.003.050.00009 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, August 9, 1982; UA003.003.050.00010 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, October 1, 1982; UA003.003.050.00011 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, January 5, 1983; UA003.003.050.00012 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, March 31, 1983; UA003.003.050.00013 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, July 30, 1983; UA003.003.050.00014 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, December 31, 1983; UA003.003.050.00015 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, March 31, 1984; UA003.003.050.00016 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, June 30, 1984; UA003.003.050.00017 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, September 30, 1984; UA003.003.050.00018 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, October 4, 1984; UA003.003.050.00019 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, December 30, 1984; UA003.003.050.00020 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, April 1, 1985; UA003.003.050.00021 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, July 13, 1985; UA003.003.050.00022 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, October 4, 1985; UA003.003.050.00023 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, December 27, 1985; UA003.003.050.00024 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, April 9, 1986; UA003.003.050.00025 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, July 2, 1986; UA003.003.050.00026 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, September 25, 1986; UA003.003.050.00027 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, December 31, 1986; UA003.003.050.00028 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, January 5, 1987; UA003.003.050.00029 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, April 2, 1987; UA003.003.050.00030 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, July 1, 1987; UA003.003.050.00031 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, October 5, 1987; UA003.003.050.00032 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, April 14, 1988; UA003.003.050.00033 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, July 1, 1988; UA003.003.050.00034 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, July 12, 1988; UA003.003.050.00035 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, October 5, 1988; UA003.003.050.00036 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, January 12, 1989; UA003.003.050.00037 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, April 7, 1989; UA003.003.050.00038 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, July 1, 1990; UA003.003.050.00039 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, January 1, 1991; UA003.003.050.00040 (Box 50)
    - IFPA, October 26, 1992; UA003.003.050.00041 (Box 50)
  - Educational Policy Committee, 1964 -- 1981; UA003.003.002
    - Educational Policy Committee, May, 1964; UA003.003.065.00001 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, 1968; UA003.003.065.00002 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, December 12, 1968; UA003.003.065.00003 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 22, 1969; April 7, 1969; May 15, UA003.003.065.00004 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 25, 1969; UA003.003.065.00005 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, December 4, 1969; UA003.003.065.00006 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 22, 1970; UA003.003.065.00007 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 11, 1970; UA003.003.065.00008 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 1, 1970; UA003.003.065.00009 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 11, 1970; UA003.003.065.00010 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, June 19, 1970; UA003.003.065.00011 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee Working Papers, June 19, 1970; UA003.003.065.00012 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee Working Papers, September 17, 1970; UA003.003.065.00013 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 18, 1971; UA003.003.065.00014 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 2, 1971; UA003.003.065.00015 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 22, 1971; UA003.003.065.00016 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 20, 1971; UA003.003.065.00017 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, June 5, 1971; UA003.003.065.00018 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 16, 1971; UA003.003.065.00019 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, October 21, 1971; UA003.003.065.00020 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, December 16, 1971; UA003.003.065.00021 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 20, 1972; UA003.003.065.00022 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, February 24, 1972; UA003.003.065.00023 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 23, 1972; UA003.003.065.00024 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 25, 1972; UA003.003.065.00025 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 28, 1972; UA003.003.065.00026 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, December 7, 1972; UA003.003.065.00027 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 18, 1973; UA003.003.065.00028 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 1, 1973; UA003.003.065.00029 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 29, 1973; UA003.003.065.00030 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 26, 1973; UA003.003.065.00031 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 24, 1973; UA003.003.065.00032 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 20, 1973; UA003.003.065.00033 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, November 15, 1973; UA003.003.065.00034 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 17, 1974; UA003.003.065.00035 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, February 21, 1974; UA003.003.065.00036 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 21, 1974; UA003.003.065.00037 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 25, 1974; UA003.003.065.00038 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 23, 1974; UA003.003.065.00039 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, June 14, 1974; UA003.003.065.00040 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 19, 1974; UA003.003.065.00041 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, October 17, 1974; UA003.003.065.00042 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, November 21, 1974; UA003.003.065.00043 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 16, 1975; UA003.003.065.00044 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, February 20, 1975; UA003.003.065.00045 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 20, 1975; UA003.003.065.00046 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 17, 1975; UA003.003.065.00047 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 15, 1975; UA003.003.065.00048 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, June 26, 1975; UA003.003.065.00049 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 11, 1975; UA003.003.065.00050 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, October 30, 1975; UA003.003.065.00051 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, November 20, 1975; UA003.003.065.00052 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 15, 1976; UA003.003.065.00053 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 18, 1976 (1), UA003.003.065.00054 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 18, 1976 (2), UA003.003.065.00055 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 29, 1976 (1), UA003.003.065.00056 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 29, 1976 (2), UA003.003.065.00057 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 13, 1976; UA003.003.065.00058 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, June 28, 1976; UA003.003.065.00059 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 16, 1976; UA003.003.065.00060 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, October 20, 1976; UA003.003.065.00061 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, December 22, 1976; UA003.003.065.00062 (Box 65)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 12, 1977; UA003.003.066.00001 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 23, 1977; UA003.003.066.00002 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, February 17, 1977; UA003.003.066.00003 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 13, 1977; UA003.003.066.00004 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 12, 1977; UA003.003.066.00005 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 15, 1977; UA003.003.066.00006 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 16, 1978; UA003.003.066.00007 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 20, 1978; UA003.003.066.00008 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 23, 1978 (2), UA003.003.066.00009 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 23, 1978 (1), UA003.003.066.00010 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 19, 1978; UA003.003.066.00011 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, October 19, 1977; UA003.003.066.00012 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 15, 1977; UA003.003.066.00013 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, June 15, 1978; UA003.003.066.00014 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 13, 1978; UA003.003.066.00015 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, October 18, 1978; UA003.003.066.00016 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, December 13, 1978; UA003.003.066.00017 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, November 15, 1978; UA003.003.066.00018 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 24, 1979; UA003.003.066.00019 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 22, 1979; UA003.003.066.00021 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 18, 1979; UA003.003.066.00022 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 16, 1979; UA003.003.066.00023 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 16, 1979; UA003.003.066.00024 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 16, 1979; UA003.003.066.00025 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, June 20, 1979; UA003.003.066.00026 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 12, 1979; UA003.003.066.00027 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, October 10, 1979; UA003.003.066.00028 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, December 12, 1979; UA003.003.066.00029 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 16, 1980; UA003.003.066.00030 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, February 13, 1980; UA003.003.066.00031 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 12, 1980; UA003.003.066.00032 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 16, 1980 (1 of 2), UA003.003.066.00033 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 16, 1980 (2 of 2), UA003.003.066.00034 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 16, 1980 (1 of 2), UA003.003.066.00035 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, April 16, 1980 (2 of 2), UA003.003.066.00036 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 14, 1980; UA003.003.066.00037 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, November 12, 1980; UA003.003.066.00038 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, October 8, 1980 (1), UA003.003.066.00039 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, September 10, 1980 (cancelled), UA003.003.066.00041 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, January 14, 1981; UA003.003.066.00042 (Box 66)
    - Educational Policy Committee, Working Papers, February 11, 1981; UA003.003.067.00001 (Box 67)
    - Educational Policy Committee, March 11, 1981; UA003.003.067.00002 (Box 67)
    - Educational Policy Committee, May 15, 1981; UA003.003.067.00003 (Box 67)